感谢Veto告诉我们选择合适的版本的重要性
Thanks for telling us about the
importance of proper dessert selection.
让我们来选择一个甜点吧
So let's choose our desserts now.
我们App支持的最早的版本是Gingerbread
The earliest platform version that
our Apple support is Gingerbread.
目前来说，选择Gingerbread意味着
At the current time, choosing
Gingerbread means we can cover over 99%
在Google Play Store激活的设备范围内我们可以覆盖99%的设备
of the devices active
on Google Playstore.
这也是能不能使用Google Play Services例如
It's also the cutoff for using Google
Play services for things like maps and
maps, location和 Android support library的分水岭
location and
the Android support library.
support library包提供了对于之后版本的UI新特性的支持
The support library package offers an
implementation of ui features that were
added in later releases of Android but
可以在老版本上使用新版本的UI
now can be used on older
versions of the platform.
所以很有用
So it's really useful.
我们选择了API 10的Gingerbread
Notice how we picked the latest
version of Gingerbread with API level
因为它相对于API 9修复了一些bug
10 because it contains additional bug
fixes that API level 9 doesn't have.
然后点击Next
The we can go ahead and click Next.
选择一个模板，我们选择Blank Activity with Fragment
We're going to choose the template,
Blank Activity with Fragment.
有一个Activity作为UI的呈现容器
For background context and
activity serves as the present layer for
上面一个Fragment占据部分屏幕来呈现内容
our UI, and a fragment represents
a behavior or portion of the screen.
我们可以修改引导为我们自动生成的文件名
And now we have an option to modify
the names of the files that will be
auto-generated from the wizard.
我们的Activity名是MainActivity
The name of our activity
is MainActivity, and
它的布局由activity_main所定义的，这是一个XML文件
the layout will come from activity_main,
which is an XML file.
同样的，Fragment的布局来自fragment_main
In a similar fashion, the fragments
layout will come from fragment_main,
也是一个XML文件
which is also an XML file.
在这里我修改下文件名为main.xml
I'm going to do a small change for
the name of the menu file to be called
因为老版本的Android Studio的默认名是这个
main.xml because on a older version of
Android's tu, that was the default name.
然后点击Finish
Then we go ahead and hit Finish.
现在你应该有一个新创建的Sunshine App
And now you should have a newly
created sunshine app with the files on
文件目录在左边
the left here.
默认情况下，你看到的文件是基于Android视图
By default, you may see
the Android view of the files,
是一个平面式的项目结构
which is a flattened version
of the project structure,
并且它高亮了你需要编辑的Android源代码文件
and it highlights the key Android
source files that you'll need to edit.
在这个课程里，我们使用这个项目视图
In this course, though, we're going to
be using the project view because that's
因为老版本中我们也是用的这个
what we had in the older
version of Android Studio.
你也可以选择你喜欢的视图
You can choose any view that you prefer,
though.
确保Gradle的编译完成了
Make sure you wait for
the gradle build to finish.
如果你有任何问题，可以去查看引导文档或者下面的笔记
If you have any errors, you can check
the guide and instructor notes below.
提示下，你还可以看下在App文件夹中的
As a tip,
you can check the build.gradle file,
build.gradle文件
which is located under the App folder.
你需要确保compileSdkVersion和
You want to make sure that
the compileSdkVersion and
targetSdkVersion都指向最新的稳定版本
the targetSdkVersion are both pointing
at the latest stable version of
the platform.
这里，最新版本是API 21也就是Android 5.0 Lollipop
In this case, it's 21 for
the Android 5.0 Lollipop release.
一旦编译好了，我们可以添加更适合我们的天气App的
Once it's done building, we can add a
custom app icon that's more fitting for
自定义的App图标
our weather app.
右击App文件夹单击新建Image Asset
Right-click on the App folder and
click New Image Asset.
你可以改变这些选项
You can choose from any of
the clip art options or
可以用下面我们提供的图片
you can use the one that we
provide in the download below.
用这个占位图标
Then, use a placeholder icon we
provide in a download below.
现在App会显示这个图标
Now this will show up in
the All Apps screen, so
点击这个图标会打开我们的App
that clicking on this app
icon will launch our app.
如果Sunshine是你最近使用的App
It will also show up in the overview
space if sunshine is one of
这个图标也会显示在多任务切换界面中
your most recent tasks.
还可以在我们App的Action Bar中看到这个图标
The other place you might see this app
icon is in the action bar of our app.
在这个课程的视频中，我们使用的是之前的
In certain videos of this course that
were filmed earlier on Kit Kat by
Kit Kat版本，默认是在Action Bar中有显示App图标
default the action bar
shows the app icon.
而在Material Design的Lollipop和之后的版本中
With material design on Lollipop and
later, the app icon doesn't show up
App图标默认不会显示，所以如果没看到它不需要担心
by default anymore, so
don't worry if you don't see it.
It's fine, and
我们将会在课程5中自定义Action Bar
we're going to be styling the action
bar later in lesson five, anyways.